

# Harshita Vudatha

Software Developer - Let's Build {...Tech, ...Innovations}

harshitavudatha@gmail.com

8639750100

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/harshita-v-1849b9162

Meticulous Software Developer with 2 years of experience in coding, debugging and project management abilities. Accomplishes project goals consistently with elegant scalable code. Works great with team members under Agile and Scrum frameworks. Seeking in keep efforts to explore in different fields and an opportunity for continuous learning.

## **Educational Background**

B-Tech (ECE)

Sagi Ramakrishnam Raju Engg College

iii 2017-2021 Percentage: 89.9 iii 2017-2021 € 2017-2021 € 2017-2021

B-Tech (ECE)

Tirumala Junior College

2015-2017 Percentage: 98.5

B-Tech (ECE) **Prasad Public School** 

i 2014-2015 Percentage: 95

#### Skills & Proficiencies

- Java
- Javascript
- · Technical and Troubleshhoting
- Software Development Life Cycle
- Data Synchronization
- Technical Documentation
- Design and Development
- Web Development
- SOL Basics
- Data Structures

### **Personality Traits**

- · Passionate towards work
- · Adept at working as part of a creative team to accomplish
- Good Inter-personal skills
- · Zeal to learn new things

#### Achievements

- GEM Award- 2022
- Team Award- 2022

## **Work Experience**

#### **HCL Tech**

Feb 2023 - Present



- Worked on Accessibility project and implemented multiple accessibility feature enhancements on the Customer Retail Banking Application.
- Learned working with tools like Axe dev accessibility and wave tools for testing the accessibility forms.
- · Used lectures, discussions and demonstrations to increase learning and classroom resources.
- classroom Worked with Software Development and testing team members to design and develop robust solutions.

#### **Temenos - Kony**

**Sept 2021 - Feb 2023** 



Hyderabad

- · Contributing in Temenos infinity product team, which ensures a smooth loan approval journey between the banks and retail clients. Delivered customization pre-built onboarding experience in 40+ countries.
- Have worked on multiple enhancements on the Customer Onboarding Bank Application.
- Designed scalable and reliable microservices, microapps, restAPI's and reusable components for solving business requirements.
- A quick learner who can adapt and learn new technologies to achieve required targets. Learned tools like Git, Maven and Eclipse.
- Integrated third party tools and components into applications.

#### Certification

- Introduction to Java Programming course by NPTEL.
- Oxford Achiever English Certification Course.
- Secured 3rd place in essay writing about Environmental Protection on National Scientific Temper Day Conducted by Jana Vignana Vedika (AP).
- Worked as Executive Body Member(EBM) of IETE- Institution of Electronics and Telecommunication Engineers Organization, an India's leading recognized professional society.